Welcome to the new Alumni Directory! If you
have an active email on file, you should have
received an email from hello.alumni@williams.edu
with a PIN and a link to set up your profile.
To get started, click the link in your email,
which will direct you to the setup page. Enter
the PIN provided in the “Temporary PIN”
box, and then input your date of birth
in the corresponding field. Confirm that
your email is correct, and click "Login."
If your PIN and date of birth match our records,
you'll be prompted to create a password. Follow
the guidelines for a secure password, re-enter
it to confirm, and then click "Set Password."
Once complete, the directory homepage
will open. For further assistance,
click “Learn More” to access FAQs,
resources, and documentation. You can
start by selecting “Setting Up Your
Profile” from the options provided.
If you didn’t receive an email with your PIN,
visit the Directory homepage and click “Create
New Login.” This will take you to the registration
page, where you can enter your information and
click "Continue." Shortly after, you’ll receive
an email with your login link and temporary PIN.
Follow the same steps: click the
link in your email, enter your PIN,
input your date of birth, and confirm your email.
Please note, if you registered using
"Create New Login," your access to
the directory will be limited until we have
verified your alumni status. Once confirmed,
you’ll receive an email notifying you
that your full access is now active.
Thank you!